export const Questions =  [
    {
      "prompt": "What is Flutter?",
      "optionA": "A new type of dance",
      "optionB": "A cross-platform mobile app development framework",
      "optionC": "A type of bird",
      "optionD": "A cooking technique",
      "answer": "optionB"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What programming language is used with Flutter?",
      "optionA": "Java",
      "optionB": "Python",
      "optionC": "Swift",
      "optionD": "Dart",
      "answer": "optionD"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What IDE is commonly used for developing Flutter apps?",
      "optionA": "Visual Studio",
      "optionB": "IntelliJ IDEA",
      "optionC": "Eclipse",
      "optionD": "Android Studio",
      "answer": "optionD"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is a widget in Flutter?",
      "optionA": "A type of user interface component",
      "optionB": "A type of data structure",
      "optionC": "A type of animation",
      "optionD": "A type of widget",
      "answer": "optionA"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is the main advantage of using Flutter for mobile app development?",
      "optionA": "Ease of development",
      "optionB": "Performance",
      "optionC": "Platform compatibility",
      "optionD": "Cost-effectiveness",
      "answer": "optionB"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is the primary purpose of the Flutter framework?",
      "optionA": "To create web applications",
      "optionB": "To create desktop applications",
      "optionC": "To create mobile applications",
      "optionD": "To create games",
      "answer": "optionC"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is the difference between Stateless and Stateful widgets in Flutter?",
      "optionA": "Stateless widgets are faster than Stateful widgets",
      "optionB": "Stateful widgets can be updated dynamically while Stateless widgets cannot",
      "optionC": "Stateless widgets have state while Stateful widgets do not",
      "optionD": "There is no difference between Stateless and Stateful widgets",
      "answer": "optionB"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is hot reload in Flutter?",
      "optionA": "A feature that allows you to restart the entire application",
      "optionB": "A feature that allows you to load new assets at runtime",
      "optionC": "A feature that allows you to reload the UI without losing the app state",
      "optionD": "A feature that allows you to reload the app state without changing the UI",
      "answer": "optionC"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is a MaterialApp in Flutter?",
      "optionA": "A widget that provides the root of the widget tree",
      "optionB": "A widget that provides the application's material design theme",
      "optionC": "A widget that provides the app bar",
      "optionD": "A widget that provides the floating action button",
      "answer": "optionB"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is a Scaffold in Flutter?",
      "optionA": "A type of widget that provides a basic visual structure for a page",
      "optionB": "A type of widget that provides data bindings for widgets",
      "optionC": "A type of widget thatprovides the app bar",
      "optionD": "A type of widget that provides an animated container",
      "answer": "optionA"
      },
      {
      "prompt": "What is a Navigator in Flutter?",
      "optionA": "A widget that displays a list of items",
      "optionB": "A widget that allows you to switch between pages",
      "optionC": "A widget that provides navigation to the settings menu",
      "optionD": "A widget that allows you to navigate to other applications",
      "answer": "optionB"
      },
      {
      "prompt": "What is a Future in Flutter?",
      "optionA": "A type of widget that provides an animated future date",
      "optionB": "A type of widget that provides future events",
      "optionC": "A type of data that represents a value that might not be available yet",
      "optionD": "A type of data that represents a value that is available immediately",
      "answer": "optionC"
      },
      {
      "prompt": "What is a Stream in Flutter?",
      "optionA": "A type of widget that provides streaming video",
      "optionB": "A type of widget that provides real-time data",
      "optionC": "A type of data that represents a sequence of events",
      "optionD": "A type of data that represents a single event",
      "answer": "optionC"
      },
      {
      "prompt": "What is an InheritedWidget in Flutter?",
      "optionA": "A type of widget that provides data to its children",
      "optionB": "A type of widget that provides UI components to its children",
      "optionC": "A type of widget that provides animation to its children",
      "optionD": "A type of widget that provides styling to its children",
      "answer": "optionA"
      }
      ]
